question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
        "question": "The most frequent subconscious activity repeated by the human body is blinking.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
        "question": "Water always boils at 100&deg;C, 212&deg;F, 373.15K, no matter where you are.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
        "question": "Salt is 100% composed of Sodium.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
        "question": "The Doppler effect applies to light.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
        "question": "Not including false teeth; A human has two sets of teeth in their lifetime.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
        "question": "A defibrillator is used to start up a heartbeat once a heart has stopped beating.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
        "question": "Igneous rocks are formed by excessive heat and pressure.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
        "question": "Anatomy considers the forms of macroscopic structures such as organs and organ systems.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
        "question": "An exothermic reaction is a chemical reaction that releases energy by radiating electricity.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
        "question": "&quot;Tachycardia&quot; or &quot;Tachyarrhythmia&quot; refers to a resting heart-rate near or over 100 BPM.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    }
]
